

# Iurie-lacob Bogdan

Game developer

# **SKILLS**

# Game development

Merning, Denmark

. 50 37 94 92

bogdan.iurie.iacob@gmail.com

https://portfolio-iurie.vercel.app

- Ability to learn and adapt
- Firm understanding of the fundamentals
- Problem solving mindset
- Clean code adept
- Testing/debugging
- Time management
- Strong collaboration skills

### UI / UX

- Wireframing
- Prototype Design
- Motion Design
- User Interface Design
- Content Writing
- User Testing

#### Sales

- Lead generation
- Market Analysis
- Client Relationship Management
- Sales and Negotiation
- Ethical Standards

# TOOLS

- HTML
- WebFlow
- CSS
- MemberStack
- React
- Blender
- Next.js
- Unity
- JavaScript
- PhotoShop
- **TypeScript**
- C#
- WordPress
- Premier Pro
- Figma

# **ABOUT**

Dedicated, self-starter developer with 3+ years of development experience in creating usercentric solutions for start-ups and individuals. Equipped with a record of success in designing and developing client's web applications, including multiple successful website launches for clients and companies. In my free time I am developing my own game, learning C#, and working on freelance platform for fashion students, and of course drink lots of Italian coffee. På god vej til at lære dansk

# **EXPERIENCE**

# YourHeadway A/S | Norway, Oslo (remote) 2023-2024

# Front-end & Business developer

- Redesigned company's brand / web page along with improving SEO and writing Blog posts for a better brand awareness & user experience
- Implemented an automation system using Apollo.io for the client outreach process resulting in contacting over 1000 leads p/m compared to 300.
- Developed copywriting strategies & optimized the technical part of sales-sequence lending to 40% increase in response rates.
- Prospected for potential new clients and turned them into increased avenues of business.

#### AppWill | Moldova (remote) 2023-2024

## Part-time Game developer

- Created detailed design documents for a variety of games in different genres like action and platformers.
- Developed, tested and iterated over 10 different prototypes, 2 of which ended up being small hits.
- Managed existing projects and helped with the development of mechanics, systems, and promotion.

# Herning Kommune | Herning April 2024

## Multimedia Designer Intern

- Conducted quantitative and qualitative research in the form of interviews, surveys, stakeholder interviews and created accurate personas based on research.
- Did an in depth dive into google analytics & SEO to find areas that need improvement implementing and suggesting potential fixes.
- Designed posters for upcoming events testing the designs with the target

#### Gamucatex | Copenhagen May 2023 - July 2023 Web developer & SoMe manager

- Redesigned and improved both the website and game page (itch.io) leading to higher
- Implemented post sqeduling using Buffer, which resulted in 50% increase in impressions on Twitter & Instagram
- Managed social media accounts by composing content, engaging with followers in comments, monitoring activities, and researching trends.

# **EDUCATION**

Multimedia Designer AP Erhvervsakademi Aarhus